It's her car. Don't tell her what to do with it.
Carjacked is a action, thriller, tv movie film directed by John Bonito.
A single mom and her child are carjacked by a bank robber
who has no intention of letting them go.
Roy, played by Stephen Dorff.
Lorraine Burton, played by Maria Bello.
Betty, played by Joanna Cassidy.
Therapist, played by Catherine Dent.
Young Mother, played by Kristen Kerr.
Deputy, played by Gary Grubbs.
Trespass is a 2011 American crime thriller film directed by Joel
Schumacher, from a screenplay by Karl Gajdusek.
It stars Nicolas Cage and Nicole Kidman as a married
couple taken hostage by extortionists.
It also stars Ben Mendelsohn, Cam Gigandet, Liana Liberato, Jordana
Spiro, Dash Mihok, Emily Meade and Nico Tortorella.
It had its world premiere at the Toronto International
Film Festival on September 14, 2011.
It was released in a limited release and through video on demand
on October 14, 2011, by Millennium Entertainment.
It is the last film to be directed by Schumacher
before his death on June 22, 2020.
The tone is intense.